

## CONTACT

- +92 322 9623932
- chtougeer410@gmail.com
- Makkah Colony, Lahore

### **EDUCATION**

2019-2023 **GOMAL UNIVERSITY** 

Bachelor in Computer Science

### SKILLS

- Interface Designing
- User Experience Design
- Interaction Designing
- Wire-framing
- Prototyping
- Problem Solving
- Story boarding
- Research & Analysis
- User-Personas Design
- Visual Communication Design
- Design Consultancy

# LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Urdu (Fluent)
- Punjabi (Basics)
- Russian (Intermediate)

# **MUHAMMAD** TOUQEER

SR. UIUX DESIGNER

## **PROFILE**

Hi! I am a dedicated and passionate person having an experience of more than 3.5 years in the field of UI/UX design working as Sr. Product Designer, Delivered 250+ projects. I care about the details and consider the motion design of affordances to be crucial in creating effective, intuitive interfaces. I like prototyping – it helps me think through interaction models and new possibilities.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

ZAPTA Technologies (Onsite)

April 2024 - Present (Full Time)

Sr. UIUX Designer

- Handling 4 Fintech Products including Web and Mobile App EMI¢
- · Collaborate with cross-functional teams to create user-centered designs for web and mobile
- applications
- · Develop wireframes, user flows, and user personas to effectively communicate design concepts

The Times Tech (Hybrid)

September 2021 - March 2024 (Full Time)

**UIUX** Designer

- · Designed intuitive user interfaces and experiences for various digital products, ensuring accessibility
- and usability
- Created detailed wireframes and prototypes, facilitating user testing and stakeholder presentations.

### LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

**GOOGLE UX Design Specialization** 

Coursera (By Google)

**Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner** 

**IBM** 

**Enterprise Design Thinking Co-Creator** 

### **TOOLS**









